52qingyuan.com 2013-05-02

# Unsubscribe

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for Unsubscribe.

This website agrees to notify you of:

  * What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identification is collected from you through the website  

  * The organization collecting the information  

  * How the information is used  

  * With whom the information may be shared  

  * What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information  

  * The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control  

  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

**Information Collection and Use**

Unsubscribe is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Unsubscribe collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

**Order**

We request information from the user on our registration, order and payment forms. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fulfill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site and is encrypted so cannot be read by any other website. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. It will also terminate once a period of time has elapsed since first using the site.

**Log Files**

We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Sharing**

We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

We use a credit card processing company to bill users for services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

**Links**

This website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.

**Security**

This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.

When our order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our accounting staff or a customer care representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information.

**Correction/Updating Personal Information**

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your postcode), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us.

**Choice/Opt-out**

If you use this site to purchase services you may occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications on our order form.

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email, or by contacting us directly.

Users of our site are notified when their information is being collected or used by any third parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require any third party, or not.

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected.

**Acceptable Use Policy**

**Goals**

Our goals are to ensure compliance with applicable law, protect network resources, preserve our and your privacy and security and maximize the usefulness of our service and the Internet.

**Interpretation**

The provisions of this policy are intended as guidelines and are not meant to be exhaustive. Generally, conduct that violates law, regulation or the accepted norms of the Internet community, whether or not expressly mentioned in this policy, is prohibited. We reserve the right at all times to prohibit activities that damage our commercial reputation and goodwill.

**Security**

Any "denial of service" attack, any attempt to breach authentication or security measures, or any unauthorized attempt to gain access to any other account, host or network is prohibited, and will result in immediate services termination, which may be without notice.

**Bandwidth Usage**

If your bandwidth either exceeds the allowance set as part of your package/service or reaches the point where it has an adverse effect on other customers we reserve the right to: disable your site, without prior notice, until you can reduce your bandwidth usage; or charge you for excess bandwidth usage, over and above your package allowance, as published by us from time to time. 

**Unacceptable Use**

  * The following use of any of our servers for the following purposes is prohibited:
  * The following use of any of our servers for the following purposes is prohibited:
  * to send bulk or unsolicited email messages (commercial or otherwise), or;
  * to collect the responses from unsolicited email, or;
  * to promote any website whose Domain Name Service is provided by us; or.
  * to post advertisements or messages that violate the charter of any newsgroup or mailing list. 
  * We reserve the right to decide whether a message violates the newsgroup or mailing list charter. In most cases we will defer to the judgment of the newsgroup or mailing list moderator or administrator.
  * Commercial messages that are appropriate under the charter of a newsgroup or mailing list, or that are expressly solicited by the recipients are permitted.
  * Conduct in connection with email or Usenet news that is an obvious nuisance (such as "mail bombing") or that would be unlawful in other contexts (for example but not limited to, threats, harassment, defamation, obscenity, or software piracy) is prohibited. 

**Forgery of Identity**

Falsifying address information or otherwise modifying headers to conceal the sender's or recipient's identity, for the purpose of circumventing this policy, is prohibited. This provision is not intended to disallow the use of aliases or anonymous remailers for any legitimate purpose.

**Copyright, Privacy, and Intellectual Property**

Using one of our hosted Domain Names to commit, aid or abet any violation of copyright or intellectual property law is prohibited. This prohibition includes publishing a private email message or that of a third party, by any means, without the express prior consent of the author.

Our and your e-mail addresses are not for sale or commercial distribution to third parties without our express prior consent or that of the subscriber.

**Cooperation with Other Providers**

Using our facilities to engage in activities that violate the terms of services of any other Internet Services Provider is prohibited. For example but without limitation, sending unsolicited commercial e-mail through our facilities to the subscribers of any Internet or online service provider that disallows unsolicited commercial email is prohibited.

**Consequences of Violation**

Violation of this policy may result in temporary suspension or permanent termination of one or more service at our sole discretion. We do not issue service credits for any outages incurred though service disablement resulting from policy violations.

**Modification**

We reserve the right to add, delete or modify any provision of this policy at any time without notice.

**Your Obligations and Warranties**

You represent, undertake and warrant to us that you will use our services for lawful purposes and only as authorised herein. In particular, you represent, warrant and undertake to us that you will:

keep secure and not disclose any password which may be given to you by us to third parties and that any such password will only be used for the authorised purpose communicated to you by us and further that you will notify us immediately of any known or suspected unauthorised use of the password. You will be liable for any unauthorised use of your password;

  * observe the procedures which we may from time to time prescribe;
  * not post, link or transmit to any of our servers any material which is unlawful, abusive, malicious, threatening, defamatory, obscene, pornographic, blasphemous or otherwise objectionable in any way;
  * not post, link or transmit to any of our servers any material which contains a virus or other hostile computer program or run any applications that could lead to a modification of the physical or logical structure of the networks being used;
  * not post, link or transmit to any of our servers any material which constitutes or encourages the commission of a criminal offence or which infringes any patent, trade mark, design rights, copyright or any other intellectual property right or similar rights of any persons;
  * adhere to laws for the protection of minors;
  * respect the privacy of others and that you will not send unsolicited, harassing, slanderous or threatening content;
  * not use any names, documents, pictures or other elements of our site so as to create the impression of any relationship whatsoever with any of our products or services, or of support for any of our products or services without our prior written consent;
  * not develop or attempt to develop programs designed to bypass the user interface to access our program functions;
  * treat all confidential and proprietary information and documents provided by us to you, including without limitation any password, as confidential and not to disclose the same to a third party.
